(Sheldon:)I'm open to the possibility.
(Sheldon:)Whatever.
(Howard:)You know, if he moves
across the hall for good,
(Howard:)Leonard could keep the
stuff you don't like
(Howard:)in Sheldon's old room.
(Howard:)Solves everything.
That's a great idea!
(Leonard:)Ooh, maybe I could turn it
into a gaming den.
(Raj:)That would be amazing.
Wait, wait,
hold on, do what?
(Sheldon:)Excuse me...
that's my room.
(Leonard:)But you won't be living here.
(Sheldon:)But that's my room.
But that's my room.
(Leonard:)You guys might want
to start eating.
(Leonard:)But you won't be living here.
(Penny:)Sweetie,
once you stop paying rent,
(Penny:)none of this is really yours.
(Sheldon:)But that's my room.
But you won't be living here!
(Sheldon:)Thank you
for understanding.
(Sheldon:)Hey, I get it.
(Sheldon:)Everybody wants to spend
more time with me.
(Sheldon:)I'm like a man made of sugar
in a world of ants.
(Amy:)Good night.
Mm, night.